<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuideApp</string>

    <!--Categories-->
    <string name="categoryCities">Cities</string>
    <string name="categoryBeaches">Beaches</string>
    <string name="categoryOtherNaturalPlaces">Other Natural Places</string>
    <string name="categoryFood">Traditional Food</string>

    <!--Beaches-->
    <string name="beachesChoroni">Choroni</string>
    <string name="beachesChoroniDescription">Choroní is a coastal locality in the far north of the
        municipality of Girardot, Aragua state, Venezuela. It is located on the outskirts of the coastal mountain range.
        This mountain range makes up the essence of the Henri Pittier National Park.</string>

    <string name="beachesLosRoques">Los Roques</string>
    <string name="beachesLosRoques_description">Los Roques National Park is a
        Venezuelan archipelago around 160 kilometers north of the capital Caracas in the Caribbean Sea.
        The protected area contains more than 300 islands and cays surrounding a 400-sq.-km lagoon.
        The archipelago’s coral reef is popular with snorkelers and scuba divers. The park is renowned
        for its isolated, white-sand beaches, windsurfing, fishing and sailing</string>

    <string name="beachesMochima">Mochima</string>
    <string name="beachesMochimaDescription">Mochima National Park is located in the States of Anzoátegui
        and Sucre (state), on the northeastern coast of Venezuela. The park covers 94,935 hectares and is
        made up of an exclusively marine area in its western sector (Anzoátegui State), a coastal marine
        area that includes the Gulf of Santa Fé and Mochima Bay, and a mountainous area that covers the Turimiquire
        Dam watershed (Sucre State). Mochima Park was created to protect the montane forests of the Turimiquire
        Range and the country\'s eastern Caribbean Sea marine landscapes, which are exceptionally beautiful.</string>

    <string name="beachesMorrocoy">Morrocoy</string>
    <string name="beachesMorrocoyDescription">Morrocoy National Park is located in the easternmost coast of Falcón
        state and northwestern of Golfo Triste, in the west central Venezuelan coast, near the towns of Boca de Aroa,
        Tucacas, Sanare, Chichiriviche, Flamenco and Tocuyo de la Costa, and consists of 32,090 acres.
        he park extends across both terrestrial and aquatic areas of Golfo Triste. It contains an area of
        mangroves and numerous islets or cays among which are Borracho, Muerto, Sombrero, Sal, Las Animas
        and Peraza, among others. There are spectaculars white sand beaches on these cays; Mero, Paiclas,
        los Juanes, Playuela, Tucupido, Azul, Boca Seca and many more. The park\'s internal bays and mangroves,
        cays and islands sit in the relief of Chichiriviche hills, with elevations of 250 m.</string>

    <string name="beachesPlayaElAgua">Playa el Agua</string>
    <string name="beachesPlayaElAguaDescription">Playa El Agua is the most famous tourist development on Margarita
        Island in Venezuela. El Agua is 2.5 miles (4 km) long, 30m wide, gold sand lined with huge palm trees
        that give shelter to numerous restaurants that provide service to diners on the beach. The boulevard at
        Playa El Agua stretches for approximately 2 miles (3 km). While there are open stretches, most of the
        ocean side is lined by restaurants and shops. This beach is favored by both locals and visitors.</string>

    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesColoniaTovar">La Colonia Tovar</string>
    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesColoniaTovarDescription">Colonia Tovar (English: Tovar Colony) is a town of Venezuela,
        capital of the municipality Tovar in Aragua state. Founded in 1843 by a group of immigrants from the then
        independent state of the Grand Duchy of Baden (later incorporated into Germany), is characterized by maintaining
        the cultural imprint of their origin, so it is called "the Germany of the Caribbean". The economy depends primarily
        on agriculture and tourism; and the town is located 42 km (26 mi) from Caracas. The Colonia is known for its
        temperate crops (peaches, strawberries, beets, cauliflower, carrots, cabbage, chard, broccoli, lettuce, onions
        and potatoes) and their derivatives.</string>

    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesGranSabana">La Gran Sabana</string>
    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesGranSabanaDescription">La Gran Sabana, English: The Great Savanna,
        also known as Guianan savanna, is a region in southeastern Venezuela.The savanna spreads into the regions of
        the Guiana Highlands and south-east into Bolívar State, extending further to the borders with Brazil and Guyana.
        The Gran Sabana has an area of 10,820 km2 (4,180 sq mi) and is part of the second largest National Park in
        Venezuela, the Canaima National Park. Only Parima Tapirapecó National Park is larger than Canaima.
        The average temperature is around 20 °C (68 °F), but at night can drop to 13 °C (55 °F) and in some
        of the more elevated sites, depending on weather, may fall a bit more. The location offers one of the most
        unusual landscapes in the world, with rivers, waterfalls and gorges, deep and vast valleys, impenetrable
        jungles and savannahs that host large numbers and varieties of plant species, a diverse fauna and the isolated
        table-top mesas locally known as tepuis.</string>

    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesLlanos">Los Llanos Venezolanos</string>
    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesLlanosDescription">One of the most beautiful regions in Venezuela is \"los llanos\",
        those huge plains where only the horizon stops your sight. Both, the vegetation and the fauna are full of beauty.
        Several ecosystems will make a trip to this region an unforgettable one.In this region there are only two very
        different seasons, where life changes completely: Rainy and dry season. In the first one, the woods, the rivers,
        the trees show all their beauty. A large part of the region is under the water. In the second one the become
        yellow and brown, and the dust covers most part of the plains, but that is when all the wildlife converges
        in the few spots where water is present. It is the season where you can see more birds and animals.
        The difference between the two seasons is so big, that you can\'t say that you know the \"llanos\" if you don\'t
        go in both periods.</string>

    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesMedanosDeCoro">Los Medanos de Coro</string>
    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesMedanosDeCoroDescription">Médanos de Coro National Park
        (Parque Nacional Los Médanos de Coro) is a Venezuelan national park located in the state of Falcón,
        near the city of Coro on the road that leads to Paraguaná. The National Park was created in 1974.
        The park is easily reached by bus or taxi from Coro. The Médanos park lies on the Isthmus of Médanos
        and covers 91 km2 (35 sq mi) of desert and coastal habitat, including salt marshes. It is made up of
        three zones: an alluvial plain, formed by the delta of the Mitare River and some smaller streams; an
        aeolian plain, composed of three types of dunes; and a littoral plain with a belt of mangrove swamps.
        The massive sand dunes, known as Médanos, spread over an area of approximately 5 by 30 km (3.1 by 18.6 mi).
        They can reach 40 m (130 ft) in height and are constantly transformed by the unrelenting wind.
    </string>

    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesPicoBolivar">El Pico Bolivar</string>
    <string name="otherNaturalPlacesPicoBolivarDescription">Pico Bolívar is the highest mountain in Venezuela,
        at 4,978 metres (16,332 ft).Located in Mérida State, its top is permanently covered with névé snow
        and three small glaciers. It can be reached only by walking; the Mérida cable car, the highest cable car
        in the world, only reaches Pico Espejo. From there it is possible to climb to Pico Bolívar. The peak is
        named after the Venezuelan independence hero Simon Bolívar. The Pico Bolívar is located on the mountain
        previously called La Columna, next to El León (4,743 m) and El Toro (4,695 m). The new name was suggested by
        Tulio Febres Cordero in 1925. It was officially renamed on December 30, 1934.</string>


    <string name="citiesCaracas">La Gran Caracas</string>
    <string name="citiesCaracasDescription">Caracas, Venezuela\'s capital,
        is a commercial and cultural center located in a northern mountain valley.
        Independence leader Simón Bolívar is buried at the National Pantheon of Venezuela,
        established in the 19th century in the city\'s old town. Caracas Cathedral, a landmark of
        Romanesque architecture, dates to the 17th century. Parque Central\'s 225m-high twin towers
        are the signature of the skyline.</string>

    <string name="citiesMaracaibo">Maracaibo</string>
    <string name="citiesMaracaiboDescription">Maracaibo is a city in northwestern Venezuela and the capital of
        Zulia state, known as the center of Venezuela\’s oil industry. Its old town is marked by colonial buildings,
        including the colorful houses lining Calle Carabobo. On central Plaza Bolívar, Maracaibo Cathedral houses the
        statue of the Cristo Negro, or Black Christ. Nearby is the 18th-century Casa de la Capitulación, a culture and
        history center.</string>

    <string name="citiesValencia">Valencia</string>
    <string name="citiesValenciaDescription">Valencia is the capital city of Carabobo State, and the third largest
        city of Venezuela. The city is an economic hub that contains Venezuela\'s top industries and manufacturing companies.</string>

    <string name="citiesPuertoLaCruz">Puerto la Cruz</string>
    <string name="citiesPuertoLaCruzDescription">Puerto La Cruz is a port city located in Anzoátegui State,
        in Venezuela. It is the seat of the Juan Antonio Sotillo Municipality. The city has road connections
        to the state capital, Barcelona, to Lecheria and to Guanta.</string>

    <string name="citiesMerida">Merida</string>
    <string name="citiesMeridaDescription">Mérida is a city in the Andes mountains of northwestern Venezuela.
        It\’s known for its Spanish colonial architecture, its parks and squares, and as a base for outdoor
        activities in the nearby Sierra Nevada and Sierra La Culata national parks. International visitors
        and the many students of the prestigious Universidad de Los Andes contribute to lively nightlife and
        cultural scenes.</string>

    <string name="foodArepa">Arepas Venezolanas</string>
    <string name="foodArepaDescription">Arepa is a type of food made of ground maize dough or cooked
        flour prominent in the cuisines of Colombia and Venezuela. It is eaten daily in those countries
        and can be served with accompaniments such as cheese (cuajada), avocado, or split to make sandwiches.
        Sizes, maize types, and added ingredients vary its preparation. Arepas can also be found in Panama and
        the Canary Islands. It is similar in shape to the Mexican gordita and the Salvadoran
        pupusa.</string>

    <string name="foodCachapa">Cachapa</string>
    <string name="foodCachapaDescription">Cachapas are a traditional Venezuelan and Colombian dish made from corn.
        Like arepas, they are popular at roadside stands. They can be made like pancakes of fresh corn dough,
        or wrapped in dry corn leaves and boiled (cachapa de hoja). The most common varieties are made with fresh ground
        corn mixed into a thick batter and cooked on a budare, like pancakes; the cachapa is slightly thicker and lumpier
        because of the pieces from corn kernels. Cachapas are traditionally eaten with Queso de Mano (hand[made] cheese),
        a soft, mozzarella-like cheese, and occasionally with fried pork chicharrón on the side. Cachapas can be very
        elaborate, some including different kinds of cheese, milky cream, or jam. They can be prepared as an appetizer,
        generally with margarine, or as a full breakfast with hand cheese and fried pork.</string>

    <string name="foodEmpanada">Empanada</string>
    <string name="foodEmpanadaDescription">An empanada is a stuffed bread or pastry baked or fried in many countries
        in Spain and Latin America. The name comes from the Spanish verb empanar, meaning to wrap or coat in bread.
        Empanadas are made by folding dough over a stuffing, which may consist of meat, cheese, huitlacoche, or other
        ingredients.</string>

    <string name="foodPabellon">Pabellon Criollo</string>
    <string name="foodPabellonDescription">Pabellón criollo is a traditional Venezuelan dish, the local version of the
        rice and beans combination found throughout the Caribbean. It is a plate of rice, shredded beef in stew and stewed
        black beans that is considered by many to be the Venezuelan national dish.</string>

    <string name="foodPatacon">Patacon</string>
    <string name="foodPataconDescription">FOR plantain lovers, it may be the best thing since sliced bread. In fact,
        a patacón (paht-ah-CONE) — the full name, patacón Maracucho, identifies its birthplace as the Venezuelan city
        of Maracaibo — is a sandwich that dispenses with bread entirely. In its place is green (that is, unripe)
        plantain that’s been sliced lengthwise, fried, pressed flat and fried again. Still warm, the golden discs embrace
        shredded beef, roast pork, chorizo, chicken or cheese.</string>

</resources>
